http://www.hhcgroup.com/privacy-statement/

New User?
Privacy Statement
This confirms that Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group is a licensee of the VeriSign Secure Site Program. Because Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group is committed to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose information regarding our privacy practices and our privacy practices conform to VeriSign's practices. By displaying the VeriSign logo, this Web site has agreed to notify you of:
1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personal identification is collected from you through the Web site
2. The organization collecting the information
3. How the information is used
4. With whom the information may be shared
5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group' control
7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our Chief Privacy Officer, Shaun Koenig, at s_koenig@hhcgroup.com.
Privacy Policy: Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group is committed to protecting the privacy of its users. The personal and medical information gathered by Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group is used to monitor and evaluate the medical charges of health care providers. Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group will not release your name, address, telephone number, emergency information or health data related to a patient's medical history to any third party without our clients consent unless, 1) you expressly direct Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group to give the information to healthcare providers, 2) Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group is required to disclose such information by law or 3) you give your name and password to someone, or 4) you provide that information in an online message board.
Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group collects and stores personal information that you provide us, including your name, address, email address and similar types of information. Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group also collects non-personal information, such as number of Web site visits, time of day when the visits occur and how long visitors stay on the Web site. This non-personal information is used to improve the Web site and to better address the needs and interests of our Web site visitors. The information collected may result in changes to information on the Web site or changes in Web site design. Non-confidential information includes any questions or answers, comments, suggestions to Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group. We can also license it to others for any purposes. These purposes include reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcast and posting, or developing, manufacturing and marketing products using such information. When you send us a comment or a question through the Web site, you automatically give Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group permission to use the information as we choose. We will not pay you for what you have written and will be able to use it in whatever ways we feel are appropriate. No personally identifiable information will be linked to the questions or answers. This general data serves to guide us as we improve our site. We may also share aggregate data with partners or other trusted third parties. Your individual identify will not be revealed.
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group uses special software to protect your privacy. All data is encrypted and transmitted over this internet site is through a secured channel established by an SSL certificate. The in-house storage of your personal information in the Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group' database is highly secure. Only employees authorized to access your data are able to do so based on a series of permission levels protected by passwords and software algorithms. All employees sign a confidentiality of data agreement at time of employment in which they agree to uphold the confidentiality of any such information. The information is not web accessible and access to the information is restricted. Users may optionally choose to have a cookie written to their hard drive for the sole purpose of remembering their user name for them. No other information will be stored in this optional user name cookie. Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications may contact us at (301) 963-0762, b_roffe@hhcgroup.com, or Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group, 438 N. Frederick Avenue, 200A, Gaithersburg, MD 20877 to opt-out. Our site gives users the option to change and modify information previously provided by going to our User Update Section to change/correct any Personally Identifiable Information. Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group does not sell, trade or rent personal information about its users. The email addresses you provide are used to respond to comments submitted through sending emails and Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group' newsletters. Subscribers to Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group must use their personal email address and Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group password.
Users that contact our site via email will not be subject to any communication from us other than as a response to the question/suggestion, unless specifically requested by the user. Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group has no control, and is not responsible for, the privacy policies of any other Web sites. If you visit "links" of Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group, you may want to read their privacy policies before providing any information.
If Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group changes its Web site privacy policy, we will list the changes here. If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. For questions or further information, contact Dr. Bruce D. Roffé (b_roffe@hhcgroup.com) at Roffé Enterprises, Inc. t/a H.H.C. Group, 438 N. Frederick Avenue, Suite 200A, Gaithersburg, MD 20877, telephone: (301) 963-0762. Last Reviewed and Updated December 17, 2010. All Rights Reserved.
ADDITIONAL SERVICES
Medical Bill Review
Medicare Reference-Based Pricing
Independent Medical Reviews and Evaluations
HHC Group has earned accreditation by URAC
(the Utilization Review Accreditation Commission) to provide internal
and external Independent Peer Reviews of medical claim grievances.
© 2020 HHC Group. All Rights Reserved.
Maximizing Savings On Medical Claims
Log In To Your Account
Forgot User ID or Password?
New User? REGISTER NOW
© 2020 HHC Group. All Rights Reserved.
